Guide to the Fuqua School of Business records, 1929-2015 UA.23.01.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Fuqua School of Business records
1929-2015
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Fuqua School of Business (Duke University)
UA.23.01.0002
27 Linear Feet
Collection includes annual reports, business associates, files on administrators, material on MBA programs, promotional materials, practicum papers, and other files. The material ranges in date from 1964-2015.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
Transfer, 2017-2019.
Historical Note
The mission of The Fuqua School of Business is to provide the highest quality education for business and academic leaders, and promote the advancement of the understanding and practice of management through research. Its first class was enrolled in 1970.
Collection Overview
Collection includes annual reports, business associates, files on administrators, material on MBA programs, promotional materials, practicum papers, and other files. The material ranges in date from 1964-1999.
Conditions Governing Access
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Conditions Governing Access
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is unprocessed and may require screening, arrangement, and/or rehousing before use. Materials have not been screened for sensitive or restricted content. Staff will need to screen materials before use. Please contact Research Services for more information.
Conditions Governing Access
This list of contents was provided by the donor and has not been verified by University Archives staff.
Business schools -- Students; Fuqua School of Business (Duke University); Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Graduate students
- Unprocessed accessions, 1
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 1)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 2)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 3)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 4)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 5)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 6)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 7)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 8)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 9)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 10)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 11)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 12)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 13)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 14)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 15)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 16)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 17)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 18)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 19)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 20)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 21)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 22)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 23)
- Accession UA2018.0057, 2
  - BA 435, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 300, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 311, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 312, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 412, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 370, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 470, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 472, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 330, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 331, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 430, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA 437, Spring 1984-1986 (Box 24)
  - BA Courses with IBM, June 1987 (Box 24)
  - IBM Study, February 1984 (Box 24)
  - GOETHE Program, 2004 (Box 24)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Administrative restriction until 2029.
  - Exchange: The Magazine of the Fuqua School of Business, Fall 1987-1992; 1994-1995 (Box 25)
  - Exchange: The Magazine of the Fuqua School of Business, Winter 1989-1992; 1995 (Box 25)
  - Exchange: The Magazine of the Fuqua School of Business, Spring 1990; 1992; 1996 (Box 25)
  - Exchange: The Magazine of the Fuqua School of Business, Summer 1986; 1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 25)
  - The Fuqua Life CD (Box 25)
  - Faculty Info Historical Charts, 1982-2001 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2026.
  - General Proposal MMS Degree, September 2006 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2031.
  - Social Enterpreneurship Initiative Progress Report, November 2001 (Box 25)
  - Global Capital Markets Strategic Plan and Audit, 2007 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2032.
  - Center for Entrepreneurship and Innovation Creation Proposal, 2015 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2040.
  - Status of Women/Minorities at Duke/Fuqua, 2002 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2027.
  - Proposal for Development of Operations Management, May 1983 (Box 25)
  - Recruiting Activities, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
  - Wes Magar-Building Dedication, 2000 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 20265
  - MOU-Seoul National University, May 2004 (Box 25)
  - Status of Women at Duke, 2002 (Box 25)
  - Health Sector Management Glaxo Grant, October 2000 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2025.
  - Guanghua Draft Proposal/Zhu Shanli, 2003 (Box 25)
    Administrative restriction until 2028.
  - CAS (Chinese Academy of Sciences), 2004 (Box 25)
  - Articles of Governance, Rev. Fac. Voting & Peterson's Doc, 1971-1983 (Box 25)
- Accession UA2019.0051, 3
  - Curriculum Committee Meeting (Box 26)
    Personnel restriction until 2070.
  - Retirement Letters (Box 26)
  - Ph.D Degree in Business Administration (Box 26)
  - Joint Degrees Program (Box 26)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 26)
  - AAA-Committee on Establishment of an Accounting Commission (Box 26)
  - MBA Program (Box 26)
  - Student Data (Box 26)
    FERPA restriction until 2070.
  - General Correspondence (Box 26)
  - Management Science Program (Box 26)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - MBA Program Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - MBA Committee Extra Reports (Box 26)
  - Faculty Meetings (Box 26)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Organizational Problems and Solutions (Box 26)
  - BOV, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Minutes--Board of Visitors, May 8, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Reports on Board of Visitors (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors, September 15-16, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors (arrangements), September 16, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors Report, May 12, 1978 (Box 26)
  - Minutes--Board of Visitors, September 16, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Minutes--Board of Visitors, March 4, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors Meeting (Original papers), March 4, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors Meeting, May 1978 (Box 26)
  - Minutes--Board of Visitors, November 18, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Minutes--Board of Visitors, May 6, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Jaedicke, Robert (Box 27)
  - Richard H. Jenrette (Box 27)
  - Pounds, William (Box 27)
  - David M. Roderick (Box 27)
  - Swan, D. O. (deceased) (Box 27)
  - Wade, Charles B, Jr. (Box 27)
  - Wagner, Harvey (Box 27)
  - Members of the Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
  - Committee Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
  - Merle E. Gilliand (Box 27)
  - Bowman, Edward H. (Box 27)
  - Winger, Maurice H., Jr. (Box 27)
  - Ray C. Adam (Box 27)
  - Mulligan, Raymond J. (Box 27)
  - C. West Churchman (Box 27)
  - Davison, Sidney (Box 27)
  - Kapnick, Harvey E. (Box 27)